# **Pradeep G. Bhosale**

## FRONT-END DEVLOPER

https://pradeepbhosle8.github.io/pradeepbhosle/

90/665, Aijnkya Society, M.H.B. Colony, Dindoshi Nager Malad East, Mumbai -97. +91 9967544174

pradeep.bhosle8@gmail.com

https://github.com/pradeepbhosle8

Creative Front-End Developer offering 4.5+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Strong technical skills as a Front-End Developer.

## **KEY SKILLS**

Front-End: Angular, React js, HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, SASS, Gulp, Bootstrap, JavaScript,

Typescript, jQuery, JSON, Ajax,

Back-End: PHP, Slim Framework, Express.js

Database: MySQL

Version Control: Git, svn tortoise

Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Carnelian Payment Networks India Pvt Ltd.

Senior Front End Developer

27 September 2021 – Present

Skills & Tools: Angular 12, Gitlab, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap

• SaaS base Product service Design and developed using Angular 12.

#### **FREELANCER**

Front End Developer

10 September 2016 – 20 September 2021

Skills & Tools: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, Materialize, Angular4+, PHP and Git.

- Designed and developed user-friendly website from initial design through completion, optimizing all cross-browser and multi-platform compatibility.
- Translated the requirements and mockups into fully functioning websites using HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript and Angular 4+.

- Responsible for building a new website for the small fleet clients and for the maintenance of the online new platform.
- Designing and Implementing HTML **email** and **websites templates** for marketing campaigns, development Clients.
- Built and implemented custom templates for blog in WordPress.

## Craftsvilla.com pvt ltd

Web Designer and Developer

1 September 2015 – 9 September 2016

Skills & Tools: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jquery, WordPress, Angular, Excel, Git

- Worked with the team, helping them build out their markup and CSS. My specialty is large scale HTML, CSS, focusing on reusability and modularity.
- Creating new Features, Functionality and capabilities on the eCommerce site using Ajax, fetch, JSON and Angular.
- Creating Modular, Responsive landing page using SASS, CSS, HTML and jQuery.
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed
- Built and implemented custom templates for Mehndi blog in WordPress.

## **Unotech Software pvt ltd**

Front End Developer, UI Developer

22 July 2013 – 29 August 2015

Skills & Tools: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jquery, JavaScript, Putty, PHP, WordPress

- Developed websites from front to backend using PHP, JavaScript, CSS and HTML.
- Enhanced user experience and accomplish webpage objectives by creating site structure, navigation, page optimization integration.
- Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages and content management systems including WordPress.
- Client project handle like. Klip.in, BSE scanning doc. Mahindra finance and insurance, PMA, Stepathlon social network, Transpure Pvt ltd etc.

### Robocom pvt ltd

Junior Web Designer, Graphic Designer

18 November 2010 – 4 June 2012

- Developed websites from scratch
- Creating Static site structure, navigation, page optimization, and integration.
- Cooperation with team members Implemented enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.

• Website design, front end development (HTML, CSS, JQuery), logo design, multimedia presentations, designing banners, and other graphic designs.

## **EDUCATION**

Mumbai University	Diploma in Graphics and Web Designing
Bachelor of Science in Botany, May 2009	2010